#### MY RESUME

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name TAN SZE NEE

GenderFemaleDate of Birth15.02.1990NationalityMalaysianResidenceSingapore PR

Address Blk 79A, Toa Payoh Central,

#14-05, Singapore 311079

Mobile Phone 98896026

Email Address joan\_tan215@hotmail.com

## **PROFILE SUMMARY**

A Certified Public Accountant (CPA Australia) with five years of working experience in the professional industry of auditing and accounting, possess multiple skills covering many financial areas such as financial analysis, financial statements, auditing practices, regulatory compliances (FRS, MAS, Companies Act), taxation, financial systems and controls. Proven track record in consistently and effectively delivering accounting services that enhance the company's purpose and profitability.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

• Position Accountant

(04/2016 to present)

**Company** Sinowealth Fund Services (S) Pte Ltd

**Responsibilities** Including but not limited to:

- Preparation of full sets of accounts (handled around 20 clients) using Quick Books and MYOB

- Preparation of fund management accounting (i.e. calculation of NAV)

- Preparation and submission of GST

- Preparation and filing of corporate income tax

- Preparation of XBRL

- Preparation of monthly payroll and CPF submission

- Preparation and review of unaudited and audited financial statements

- Involve in internal audit of RFMC and CMS licensed companies (application of MAS regulations)

- Practical application of Singapore Financial Reporting Standards (SFRS), IFRS and Companies Act

#### Position

Senior Auditor

(11/2014 to 01/2016)

# Company

Paul Hooi & Company

# Responsibilities

Including but not limited to:

- Oversee and involve in full cycle of audit procedure
- Oversee the audit quality control section of the firm
- Handle audit scheduling and people management
- Practical application of Singapore Financial Reporting Standards (SFRS), IFRS and Companies Act
- Preparation and review of group consolidation worksheet
- Team leader of MNC audit engagements
- Leading team to overseas engagements (eg. Australia, Shanghai etc)
- Involve in full spectrum of Singapore government school (MOE) internal audit engagements
- Preparation of financial statements and compilation reports
- Review and analyse clients' accounting records and management reports

#### Position

Audit Senior Associate (03/2012 to 08/2014)

#### **Company**

Ernst & Young – Malaysia (Kuching)

#### Responsibilities

Including but not limited to:

- Oversee and involve in various assurance engagements (industries involved including manufacturing, education, utility, construction and etc)
- Review clients' internal controls to identify control deficiencies
- Analyse and evaluate the accuracy of accounting systems and procedure
- Sound knowledge of practical application of Malaysian Financial Reporting Standards (MFRS), International Financial Reporting Standards (IFRS) and Private Entities Reporting Standards in Malaysia
- Ability to work under pressure and in meeting deadlines
- Actively participate in the Firm's corporate social responsibilities' activities
- Well skilled in the preparation of the financial statements

Position Trainee

(01/2011 to 02/2011)

**Company** Ernst & Young – Malaysia (Kuching)

**Responsibilities** Assist seniors in providing audit and assurance services

Position Part Time Tutor/ Clerk

(01/2009 to 06/2009)

**Company** Bina Jaya Tuition School

**Responsibilities** Involve in paper work, answering phone calls and teaching

Chinese, English, Maths and Science (Form 1 and Form 2)

# **EDUCATION QUALIFICATIONS**

2012 – 2015 Certified Public Accountant (CPA) Australia

(Professional Certificate)

■ 2009 – 2011 Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting)

Swinburne University of Technology

Major in Accounting Minor in Finance CGPA: 3.7/4.0

2003 - 2008 Unified Examination Certificate (UEC)

Chung Hua Middle School No. 1 Programme: Arts/Commerce

Results: 12 As and 1 B (13 papers in total)

2005 – 2007
Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)

Chung Hua Middle School No. 1 Programme: Arts/Commerce

Results: 8 As and 2 Bs (10 papers in total)

## OTHER PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENTS

2008 Completion of LCCI Level 2 with Distinction

Completion of User Business System(UBS) in:

Computerised AccountingComputerised Stock Control

- Computerised Payroll

2007 Completion of Education Ordinary Level:

English Language – 1119 (A2)

## **SKILLS AND ABILITIES**

Software Experience

ERP system
Quick Books, IFCA Accounting Software, UBS, MYOB

and basic SAP Accounting System

**Computer Skills** 

Microsoft Office Proficient in Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel and

Microsoft Power Point

**Self Management Skills** 

■ **Team player** Co-operate well with other members in team discussions

and team building

Leadership Team leader for different engagements (listed companies

and private entities) in EY as well as in Paul Hooi & Co.

Responsible
Fulfill responsibilities as a leader such as reasonable task

allocation and ensure a well-organized progress

■ **Time management** Timely submission of work assigned for review and also

meeting all the tight deadlines

Meticulous, organised, attention to details

Languages Skills

Language Proficient in spoken and written English, Chinese, Malay

■ **Dialect** Cantonese, Hokkien and Teochew (spoken)

**EXPECTED SALARY** 

■ **Expected** SGD 4,400

LAST DRAWN SALARY

■ Last drawn SGD 3,900

# **REASONS FOR LEAVING**

- To look for better career opportunity and growth in the commercial line
- To gain more diversified experience for my long term career development

# **AVAILABILITY**

One month notice

## REFEREE

Harry Ting Sze Kion

Company: Amicorp Trustees (Singapore) Limited

Position: Finance Manager

Liu Tonin

Company: Ernst & Young Malaysia

Position: Audit Manager